Magna Carta, that's the power that can cause earthquakes or make it rain.
But you need a bunch of sacred treasures to make it work, right?
Yes, the more of the sacred treasures you possess, the more power you can call forth.
If we could use the Magna Carta, then we could get revenge on the Yossil.
You will never be able to use the Magna Carta if you think like that.
Why not?
The Magna Carta is unbelievably powerful.
Unless you have the necessary training, you won't be able to use it.
Then I'll become stronger.
Listen, Mano, the Magna Carta can be evoked regardless of one's strength.
But first, you must understand how this world works.